{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4855","name":"GO! Smoothies, LLC","address":"110 Clifford","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Calestro Bradford","licenseNumber":"203688","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"5/31/2017","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Permanently Closed","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","geom":"0101000020E610000024A1E81232C354C0388D9B24DA2A4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"38996","establishmentid":"4855","name":"GO! Smoothies, LLC","inspectionDate":"2017-06-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"5","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"5","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38996","inspectionDate":"6/13/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4855","name":"GO! Smoothies, LLC","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"Floor(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Worn spots","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"38996","inspectionDate":"6/13/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4855","name":"GO! Smoothies, LLC","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"wall(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"UPPER STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"At the Wall (South)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"38996","inspectionDate":"6/13/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4855","name":"GO! Smoothies, LLC","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"38996","inspectionDate":"6/13/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4855","name":"GO! Smoothies, LLC","violationCode":"6-304.11","violationDescription":"If necessary to keep rooms free of excessive heat, steam, condensation, vapors, obnoxious odors, smoke, and fumes, mechanical ventilation of sufficient capacity shall be provided.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Mechanical ventilation","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"Missing Mechanical ventilation","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"38996","inspectionDate":"6/13/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4855","name":"GO! Smoothies, LLC","violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"UPPER STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"On the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."}]},{"inspectionid":"36923","establishmentid":"4855","name":"GO! Smoothies, LLC","inspectionDate":"2016-10-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"2","ccount":"5","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"5","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36923","inspectionDate":"10/28/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4855","name":"GO! Smoothies, LLC","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"drain line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Under the Three compartment sink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"36923","inspectionDate":"10/28/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4855","name":"GO! Smoothies, LLC","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Missing Test strips","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"36923","inspectionDate":"10/28/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4855","name":"GO! Smoothies, LLC","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"Floor(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"36923","inspectionDate":"10/28/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4855","name":"GO! Smoothies, LLC","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"ceiling(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"UPPER STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"At the Ceiling (s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"36923","inspectionDate":"10/28/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4855","name":"GO! Smoothies, LLC","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"wall(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"UPPER STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"At the Wall(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"36923","inspectionDate":"10/28/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4855","name":"GO! Smoothies, LLC","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"36923","inspectionDate":"10/28/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4855","name":"GO! Smoothies, LLC","violationCode":"5-202.12","violationDescription":"(A) A handwashing sink shall be equipped to provide water at a temperature of at least 38°C (100°F) through a mixing valve or combination faucet. (Pf)  \r\n(B) A steam mixing valve may not be used at a handwashing sink.  \r\n(C) A self-closing, slow-closing, or metering faucet shall provide a flow of water for at least 15 seconds without the need to reactivate the faucet.   \r\n(D) An automatic handwashing facility shall be installed in accordance with manufacturer's instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"front","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4855"}}